[
  {
    "question": "syal",
    "answer": "scarf"
  },
  {
    "question": "dasi",
    "answer": "tie"
  },
  {
    "question": "topi",
    "answer": "hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaus",
    "answer": "t-shirt"
  },
  {
    "question": "kaus kaki",
    "answer": "socks"
  },
  {
    "question": "sepatu",
    "answer": "shoes"
  },
  {
    "question": "sarung tangan",
    "answer": "gloves"
  },
  {
    "question": "jaket",
    "answer": "jacket"
  },
  {
    "question": "tas",
    "answer": "bag"
  },
  {
    "question": "dompet",
    "answer": "wallet"
  },
  {
    "question": "pakaian",
    "answer": "clothes"
  },
  {
    "question": "celana",
    "answer": "pants"
  },
  {
    "question": "kantong",
    "answer": "pocket"
  },
  {
    "question": "sabuk",
    "answer": "belt"
  },
  {
    "question": "kemeja",
    "answer": "shirt"
  },
  {
    "question": "payung",
    "answer": "umbrella"
  },
  {
    "question": "rok",
    "answer": "skirt"
  },
  {
    "question": "gaun",
    "answer": "dress"
  }
]